Xu Xiaofeng
徐曉峰
You don't deserve to be a father
你不配當一個父親
Why do you say I don't deserve it?
憑什麼說我不配
That's my child
那是我孩子
I want to see him
我想見他
Is there anything wrong?
有錯嗎
You are wrong
你錯就錯在
Children should not be used as bargaining chips
不該拿孩子當籌碼
To change the future of a mistress
去換小三的前程
Susu, she
素素她
is not a mistress.
不是小三
What is that?
那是什麼
Dowry
陪嫁嗎
or
還是
your bed companion?
你的陪床
You little cutie
你個小可愛
What to say
說什麼呢
stop
住手
What are you going to do to my son?
你們要把我兒子怎麼樣
Son
兒子
Zhang Qin
張沁
Come and hit me if you dare
有種你來打我
This is the first time I've heard of it
我還是第一次聽說
There is such a requirement
有這種要求
OK
好啊
Then I will satisfy you
那我就滿足你